<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>fiction on Nether Skin</title><link>https://nether-skin.github.io/tags/fiction/</link><description>Recent content in fiction on Nether Skin</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2023 02:26:10 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nether-skin.github.io/tags/fiction/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Unbound narratives. A dive.</title><link>https://nether-skin.github.io/articles/unbound-narratives/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2023 02:26:10 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://nether-skin.github.io/articles/unbound-narratives/</guid><description>Words that bless the eye that reads them, Telling of a future beyond the reach of fear. Scroll of Avacyn
First things first: It is not this essay’s mission to discredit, harm, or conjure up the demise of any authors, as suggested (and done) by writers before me. An example: In The Death of the Author (1967),1 Roland Barthes strongly condemns the oversaturated presence of authors in their work, proclaiming that writing inevitably becomes irreducible to the person(s) it was produced by.</description></item><item><title>Yes Future. Experimental Urban Cryptology</title><link>https://nether-skin.github.io/articles/experimental-urban-cryptology/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2023 02:26:10 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://nether-skin.github.io/articles/experimental-urban-cryptology/</guid><description>1. Closed-source city In Paris, in the subway, feeling a new skin. In the RER too. This station has been completely rebuilt since last time, but they haven&amp;rsquo;t managed to get rid of that sewage smell. The underground remains disturbing, even with the new walls. Trapped under the earth‘s surface, carried away by flows of people, running under artificial lights.
Old water drainage marks, pixelated skies of cheesy ads for Irish whisky and one-eyed screens on the walls.</description></item><item><title>Into the Great White North</title><link>https://nether-skin.github.io/articles/into-the-great-white-north/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 02:26:10 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://nether-skin.github.io/articles/into-the-great-white-north/</guid><description>a bulging syphilitic brain with a pink leech dangling at the root of it
You’ve been consumed by Cyclonopedia.
The plane of the Thing is characterized by lack of any cognition about the self despite total control from first or third person perspectives, dissociative fugue syndrome, mirroring and the total immersion of player or reader into the Ludicosm or the game-space. (244) You close your book on page 244 and turn toward quiet reflection.</description></item></channel></rss>